<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.4.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-04-14T21:33:10-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/</id><title type="html">collegebysarah</title><subtitle>Because College is Difficult</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Siblings and Learning to Drive</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Siblings-Driving/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Siblings and Learning to Drive" /><published>2016-06-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2016-06-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Siblings-Driving</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Siblings-Driving/">&lt;p&gt;Growing up, my siblings and I would dream about the day we were old enough to drive; it seemed like the ultimate symbol of freedom. Being able to drive was being independent; going where you want to go, leaving when you want to, not being dependent on parents to drive you places. All of us were so excited to obtain that freedom.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I think deep down, this strong desire to drive was connected to the fact that all of us had things we wanted to do. We weren’t content just living, we wanted to travel and figure out what life was like outside our neighborhood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I never thought that this freedom would end up breaking my heart. Now, we’re all grown up, we all have full time jobs, our own group of friends, and half of us live in different states.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently had to say goodbye to my brother and sister in law who moved to California, and in a few months my younger brother is going to do the same. My older sister and brother in law currently reside in Iowa, which leaves my younger sister and I (along with my fiance) at home.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a strange feeling having the people who love you most leave. I can no longer stop by my brothers office and say hi or eat donuts with him. Pretty soon, I won’t be able to bribe my younger brother for coffee because of his barista status. I can’t text my older sister that I’m coming over because I’m bored. Family Sunday lunches are pretty pathetic. We currently survive by group texts and face time, which I never thought would happen when I was younger.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t get me wrong, I am so proud of my siblings; they are my heroes and my biggest fans. But growing up includes letting go, and that is hard to face.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Growing up, my siblings and I would dream about the day we were old enough to drive; it seemed like the ultimate symbol of freedom. Being able to drive was being independent; going where you want to go, leaving when you want to, not being dependent on parents to drive you places. All of us were so excited to obtain that freedom.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">You’re up and running!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Hello-World/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="You're up and running!" /><published>2014-03-03T00:00:00-06:00</published><updated>2014-03-03T00:00:00-06:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Hello-World</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Hello-World/">&lt;p&gt;Next you can update your site name, avatar and other options using the _config.yml file in the root of your repository (shown below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/config.png&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The easiest way to make your first post is to edit this one. Go into /_posts/ and update the Hello World markdown file. For more instructions head over to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/barryclark/jekyll-now&quot;&gt;Jekyll Now repository&lt;/a&gt; on GitHub.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Next you can update your site name, avatar and other options using the _config.yml file in the root of your repository (shown below).</summary></entry></feed>